Independent and self-driven, I have close to 4 years of experience in IT operations and 3 years of work experience in logistics industry. I have a proven track record of working with customers and vendors. I am currently enrolled in Logistics and Supply Chain Management course in SUSS and am keen to join the industry.

Education

Singapore University of Social Sciences

2019-Present

• Bsc Logistics and Supply Chain Management

Temasek Polytechnic

2013-2016

• Diploma in Information Technology

Coral Secondary School

2008-2012

• 'O' Levels

Work Experience

Associate Engineer at ST Engineering Advanced Network & Sensors Pte.Ltd June 2018 – Present

- Responsible for carrying out corrective and preventive maintenance of communications devices for Singapore defence force.
- **Lead a team of six** to perform daily tasking, fault and consistently achieved at least 75% distinction in the competency tests.
- Liaise and maintain good relationships with external vendors to ensure equipment maintenance service level agreements are achieved
- Develop work procedures to ensure team consistently achieves zero work accident.
- Support customer service team on equipment servicing and maintenance issues.
- In charge of preparing monthly servicing and analysis reports to monitor team performance and identify improvement opportunities

Operations Trainee at CX Logistics

January 2013 – July 2016

- Operational delivery and routine packing activities for the warehouse
- Responsible for quality check on items before and after events
- Documentation for LCL shipment during loading and unloading

Skills

Language skills: Highly proficient in both written and spoken English and Chinese

Software: Microsoft Powerpoint, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, Visual Studio, Sql Server Management Studio, MySql WorkBench

Programming language: Java, C#

Web Development: HTML, Php, Adobe Photoshop, Ajax technologies, CS